Leonard. Leonard.
(Scene:)Leonard.
Sheldon, it's 2:00 in the morning.
Why does everybody keep telling me
what time it is?
- Everybody?
- You, the president of the university...
(Sheldon:)...his wife,
their sullen teenage daughter.
(Sheldon:)That entire family is fascinated by what
time it is and whether people know it.
(Leonard:)You went to President Seibert's house
in the middle of the night?
(Sheldon:)He didn't respond to my e-mail,
his phone number is unlisted.
(Sheldon:)Tell me what my other option was.
(Leonard:)You could have waited until morning.
(Leonard:)I know, look who I'm talking to.
(Sheldon:)Remember the grant proposal I submitted
to the National Science Foundation...
(Sheldon:)...to detect slow-moving monopoles
at the magnetic north pole?
(Leonard:)Hardly a day goes by
when I don't think about it.
Oh, how nice.
(Sheldon:)Well, a space opened up
at the last minute...
(Sheldon:)...on the NSF expedition
to the Arctic Circle.
(Leonard:)Wait a minute.